Guide to the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum B
Yale University Divinity School Library
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia Records - Addendum B
1938-1988
RG 11B
Yale University Divinity School Library
68
(164 boxes)
This record group represents a continuation of the official archives of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, supplementing and overlapping the papers in record groups 11 and 11A. It provides extensive information about the institutions and projects to which the United Board lent its support. The United Board for Chrisian Higher Education in Asia supports educational work in China, Hong Kong, India, Indonesia, Japan, Korea, Pakistan, The Philippines, Republic of China (Taiwan).
United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia
Conditions Governing Access
Open to qualified researchers.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Deposited by the UBCHEA.
Biographical / Historical
Detailed information about the work of the United Board for Christian Higher Education during the period represented by these archives is contained in Paul Lauby's book Sailing on Winds of Change: Two Decades in the Life of the United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1969-1990.
Scope and Contents
II. United Board Consolidated General File
III. New File
IV. College Files
V. Audio-visual Materials
The researcher should be aware not only of the interrelatedness between Groups 11A and 11B, but also of the interrelatedness betweeen the series within Group 11B. Some cross referencing has been used to point out cases of diffused documentation, but a general awareness of its prevalence in this collection is also advised. Eight additional pages of cross-references are included in a folder preceding Folder 1.
This record group documents the operations and program of the United Board for Christian Education in Asia, but also provides insight into a variety of more general topics. Detailed reports and correspondence document Asian nationalism in the 1960s and 1970s, the universities as fomenters of radical movements against right-wing governments in Korea, Taiwan, the Philippines, and Indonesia, and the role of churches in supporting these radical movements. The role of families such as the Rockefellers and Luces in the interplay of American Christianity and philanthropy is documented. Insight is provided on American cold war attitudes toward Southeast Asia and how they were sustained. An interesting set of fact sheets regarding human rights issues is filed under Korea in Series I.
Series II represents the office files of the New York headquarters of the United Board. The materials remain in their original arrangement, filed alphabetically by the names of individuals, organizations, countries, or subject headings. There are in this Series some materials relating to various colleges, listed under the names of the countries in which they are located. The United Board had less extensive interaction with these colleges listed in Series II, compared to the colleges listed in Series IV, College Files. Prominent correspondents in Series II include: John K. Fairbank, William P. Fenn, Sidney and Elizabeth Gamble, Lyman Hoover, Walter Judd, Henry R. Luce, Henry Luce III, Elisabeth Luce Moore, I. M. Pei, and Henry P. Van Dusen.
While the Consolidated General File of Series II is primarily correspondence, Series III, New File, contains primarily official papers, minutes, and reports. There are, however, Executive Director reports filed under Paul T.Lauby in Series II. Minutes of the Board of Trustees and various standing and specialized committees in Series II provide an overview of the activities and programs of the United Board. Of particular interest is a collection of correspondence and documents relating to the Communist takeover of the China colleges and universities in 1950-1951.
Correspondence, minutes, reports and publications in Series IV, College Files, document the policy and programs of colleges and universities in Asia which were associated with the United Board. Material from twenty institutions is included, but the files are most extensive for the following schools:
Satya Wacana Christian University, Indonesia
Silliman University, The Philippines
Tunghai University, Taiwan
Yonsei University, Korea
A complete listing of institutions documented can be found on page 58.
Materials from or concerning related organizations, such as those found in Series VI of Record Groups 11 and 11A, are located in Series II, the Consolidated General File, of this record group.
Arrangement
II. United Board Consolidated General File
III. New File
IV. College Files
V. Audio-visual Materials
Religious education -- Asia; Universities and colleges -- Asia; Educators; Chong Ji shu yuan (Hong Kong, China); Council on Christian Higher Education in Asia (U.S.); Dong hai da xue; Princeton-Yenching Foundation; Silliman University; United Board for Christian Higher Education in Asia; Yŏnse Taehakkyo
- United Board Consolidated General File, Series II
  Scope and Contents
  This file is alphabetically arranged. Headings include topics, individual names, and names of organizations. The original order and heading designations of the file have not been changed. The time period covered by this file overlaps slightly with that of the similar file found in Series II of Record Group llA.
  - A - Az (Box 1, Folder 1,2)
  - Aetna Life Insurance Co., 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agricultural Development Council, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agricultural Missions Inc., 1979 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Allen Memorial Building Fund, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - American Bureau for Medical Advancement in China, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Anderson, Delbert E., 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Gerald H., 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Anglican Church in Korea, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Anh, Le Thi, 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Annual Dinner, 1971-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Appleton, Frederic G., Jr. and Sr., 1971-1979 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Arnold, Charles H. - Estate of, 1965-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Asher, Eva, 1975-1979 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Asia Foundation, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Asia Society, 1973-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Asian Institute of Theology, 1971-1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Asian Women's Institute, 1972-1979 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Association of Christian Universities and Colleges in Asia, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Association of Psychological and Educational Counsellors in Asia, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Atkinson Foundation, 1971-1978 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Ba - Bz (Box 3, Folder 27,28)
  - Banister Trust, 1971-1979 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Barker, Lee V., 1971-1979 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Barnett, Redmond J. and Suzanne W., 1973 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bates, Miner Searle, 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Beechy, Atlee, 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Beloso, Raoul H., Memorial Fund, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Bennett, Rexie E. - Estate of, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Beran, George W. and Janice, 1973-1979 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Berger, Marie Cole, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Berger, Marie Cole, Memorial Fund, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Best, Ernest E., 1974-1979 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Bibliographies, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Biggs, John, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Bintoro, 1974-1978 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Bovenkerk, Henry G., 1972-1978 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Breece, Ruth P. - Estate of, 1973-1976 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Ca - Cz (Box 4, Folder 45-47)
  - California Academy of Sciences, 1971-1975 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Cameron, James A., 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Cammack Associates (UBCHEA pension plans), 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Campbell, Margaret Shaw - Estate of, 1973-1978 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Carlander, Kenneth, 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Carle, Kenneth, 1972-1974 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Carson, Arthur L., 1975-1979 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Chandi, P. T., 1968-1979 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Chen drawings, pre 1972 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Chen, Kenneth K. S.; Willow Chen Memorial Scholarship, 1971-1976 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Chen, Theodore H. E., 1972-1978 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Chiang Kai-shek, Madame, 1966,n.d. (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Chien, Jeanette Hsu, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - China, Republic of, Diplomatic offices; incl. James C.H. Shen, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - China Graduate School of Theology, 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - China Medical Board of New York, 1967-1978 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - China Medical Board Endowment Fund for Med. Research at Yonsei Med. College, 1976-1978 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - China: A - L (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - China: Liu (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - China: S - Zhang (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - China: Zhao - Zhu (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - China:Immaculate Heart College Library Sale, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - China:Institute for Research on World Religions, 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 70,71)
  - China:Joint Committee on Contemporary China / Social Science Research Council, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - China: Kung, Samuel S. / Science Technology Review, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 73)
  - China: Liu, Xie-he, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 74)
  - China: Lo, Irving, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - China: Mashberg, Michael, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 76)
  - China: Museum of the American Indian, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 77)
  - China: National Association of Foreign Student Affairs, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 78)
  - China: National Council of the Churches of Christ, China Program, 1980-1981 (Box 6, Folder 79)
  - China: Population Reference Bureau, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 80)
  - China: Sailer, Randolph, 1973-1982 (Box 6, Folder 81)
  - China: Scovel, Thomas and Janene, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 82)
  - China: Slide set orders, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 83)
  - China: SUNY China program, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 84)
  - China: Sun, Chen-kao, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 85)
  - China: United Methodist Bd. of Global Ministries, China Program, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 86)
  - China: U.S. - China Education Clearing House, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 87)
  - China: U.S. - China Peoples Friendship Association, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 88)
  - China: U.S. Embassy, Beijing, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 89)
  - China: Wei, Qiwen, 1980 (Box 7, Folder 90)
  - China: Wu, Qianzhi, 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 91)
  - China: Wu, Tsung-su, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 92)
  - China: Yamada, Ken (United Methodist Bd. of Higher Education and Ministry), 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 93)
  - China: Yang, Zongsui, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 94)
  - China: Yeh, Victor C. / International Cyber Machines Corp., 1981 (Box 7, Folder 95)
  - China: Zhu, Hong, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 96)
  - Ching, Julia, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 97)
  - Chou, Ruth Huie, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 98)
  - Christian Conference of Asia, 1962-1979 (Box 8, Folder 99)
  - Christmas cards, 1962-1974 (Box 8, Folder 100)
  - Chu, Y. K., 1972-1975 (Box 8, Folder 101)
  - Chung Yuan Christian College of Science and Engineering, Taiwan, 1971-1978 (Box 8, Folder 102)
  - Church of Christ, Union (formerly Berea), 1971-1979 (Box 8, Folder 103)
  - Church Women United, 1975-1978 (Box 8, Folder 104)
  - Citibank, New York, 1970-1979 (Box 8, Folder 105)
  - Claremont Committee of the UBCHEA, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 106)
  - Clymer, Kenton, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 107)
  - Coles, J. Ackerman - Estate of, 1968-1979 (Box 8, Folder 108)
  - Commission for the Advancement of Christian Higher Education in Asia (CACHEA) -Reports, 1970-1973 (Box 8, Folder 109,110)
  - CACHEA -"Program for Advance...", 1969 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - CACHEA -Minutes, reports, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 112)
  - CACHEA -Correspondence, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 113)
  - CACHEA -Minutes, reports, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 114)
  - CACHEA -Correspondence, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 115)
  - CACHEA -Corres. reports, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 116)
  - CACHEA -Financial records, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 117)
  - Conard family, 1974-1979 (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Conference sites, 1971,1979 (Box 10, Folder 119)
  - Conferences 1971 - 1976: see: Fellows Conferences
  - Conference - Wingspread / Asian faculty, 1978 (Box 10, Folder 120,121)
  - Conference Board of Assoc. Research Councils, 1961-1963 (Box 10, Folder 122)
  - Conference of Missionary Societies in Great Britain and Ireland, 1955-1971 (Box 10, Folder 123)
  - Conference on Christian Higher Education in Asia, New York, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 124)
  - Congdon, Mrs. Edward C., 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 125)
  - Congdon, Elisabeth - Trust Fund, 1964-1977 (Box 10, Folder 126)
  - Conrow, Marion, 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 127)
  - Constans-Culver Foundation, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 128)
  - Continental Can Co., 1960-1966 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Cooley, Frank L., 1973-1977 (Box 10, Folder 130)
  - Cooper, Clara Chassell, 1963-1972 (Box 10, Folder 131)
  - Corbett, Charles H., 1961-1964 (Box 11, Folder 132)
  - Corbett, Dorothy, 1962-1964 (Box 11, Folder 133)
  - Corbett, Elizabeth M. and Richard, 1977-1979 (Box 11, Folder 134)
  - Corbitt, Duvon, 1971-1974 (Box 11, Folder 135)
  - Cornelio, Josefina S., 1977-1981 (Box 11, Folder 136)
  - Corporate Contributions, Inc., 1978 (Box 11, Folder 137)
  - Corson, Peter, 1961-1978 (Box 11, Folder 138)
  - Council for Advancement of Small Colleges, Inc., 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 139)
  - Council of Protestant Colleges and Universities, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 140)
  - Council on Christian Higher Education in Asia, 1960 (Box 11, Folder 141)
  - Crabtree, Loren W., 1969-1973 (Box 11, Folder 142)
  - Craig, Earle M., 1967-1975 (Box 11, Folder 143)
  - Crawford, Louise, 1971-1976 (Box 11, Folder 144)
  - Cressey, George B. and wife, 1959-1975 (Box 11, Folder 145)
  - Cressey, Paul and Elizabeth, 1963-1979 (Box 11, Folder 146)
  - Cross, Laura B., Memorial Fund and Rowland Cross, 1961-1978 (Box 11, Folder 147)
  - Crummey, John D., 1964-1969 (Box 11, Folder 148)
  - Culver, Agnes G., Trust, 1962-1973 (Box 11, Folder 149)
  - Curran, Jean Alonzo, 1965-1977 (Box 11, Folder 150)
  - Curran, J.A. -Reports on Yonsei University College of Medicine, 1961-1963 (Box 11, Folder 151)
  - Curran, J.A.-Progress report on Yonsei Univ. College of Medicine and Severance Hospital, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 152)
  - Curtis, Carolyn, 1973-1977 (Box 12, Folder 153)
  - Da - Dz (Box 12, Folder 154-158)
  - Dadisman, Elizabeth, 1969-1973 (Box 13, Folder 159)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1965-1975 (Box 13, Folder 160)
  - Danforth, Mrs. N. Loring, 1960-1969 (Box 13, Folder 161)
  - Dartmouth College: Project Asia, 1964-1970 (Box 13, Folder 162)
  - Daugherty, Ruth, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Davidson College, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Davis, Arthur Vining, Foundation, 1967-1974 (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - Davis, Charles J. R. / Foster-Davis Foundation, 1967-1979 (Box 13, Folder 164A)
  - Davis, Deborah, 1967-1976 (Box 13, Folder 165)
  - Davis, Hugh E., Jr., 1967-1974 (Box 13, Folder 166)
  - Decker, John W., 1966-1979 (Box 13, Folder 166)
  - Deckert, Marion, 1975-1978 (Box 13, Folder 167)
  - Defeno, Emily, 1960-1962 (Box 13, Folder 167)
  - De Groot, Louis L., 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - De Jong, Mary C., 1966-1967 (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - Del Carmen, Rolando V., 1977-1979 (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Denlinger, Paul B., 1961 (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - Denny, Wayne B., 1970-1979 (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - De Sainte Phalle, Thibaut, 1965-1976 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - DeWolf, L. Harold, 1971-1974 (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - Dickinson, Raymond L., 1959-1978 (Box 14, Folder 172)
  - Dickinson, Richard, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 172)
  - Diener, Paul W., 1965-1973 (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Diesto, Severino, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Dime Savings Bank, 1971-1978 (Box 14, Folder 174)
  - Dippel, John V. H., 1968-1979 (Box 14, Folder 174)
  - Dirks, J. Edward, 1965-1973 (Box 14, Folder 175)
  - Dixon Community Church, 1961-1968 (Box 14, Folder 176)
  - Documentation for Action Groups in Asia (DAGA), 1974-1977 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - Doh, Byung Il, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - Dong, Wonmo, 1972-1973 (Box 14, Folder 178)
  - Donovan, Dorothy and Hedley, 1967-1978 (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - Dorn, Jared and Minda, 1970-1979 (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Doster, Howard, 1968-1971 (Box 14, Folder 181)
  - Dreyfus Foundation, 1967-1979 (Box 14, Folder 182)
  - Druding, Leonard, 1967-1979 (Box 14, Folder 183)
  - Dunkin, Ida S. Howard F., Memorial Endowment Fund, 1963-1974 (Box 14, Folder 184)
  - Dunn, A. Eleanor, 1965-1979 (Box 14, Folder 185)
  - Durrant, Edna D., 1971-1977 (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - Dwight, Robert, 1981 (Box 14, Folder 186)
  - Ea - Ez (Box 15, Folder 187-191)
  - Early, Willa B., 1959-1960 (Box 15, Folder 192)
  - East Bay Committee, 1969-1979 (Box 15, Folder 193-197)
  - East Liberty Presbyterian Church, 1962-1970 (Box 16, Folder 198)
  - East-West Center, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 199)
  - Eaton, Carol B., 1960 (Box 16, Folder 200)
  - Echano, Roman A., 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 201)
  - Ecumenical Development Cooperative Society, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 202)
  - Edipa Foundation, 1964-1974 (Box 16, Folder 203)
  - Educational Council for Foreign Medical Graduates, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 204)
  - Eerdmans, William B., Jr., 1971-1981 (Box 16, Folder 205)
  - Eldridge, Ann, 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 206)
  - Ellis, Mildred, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 207)
  - Elrod, Jefferson McRee, 1964-1966 (Box 16, Folder 208)
  - Elston, Arla, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 209)
  - Emory University, 1963-1981 (Box 16, Folder 210)
  - Endowment maintenance funds / Endowments held by others, 1963,1969 (Box 16, Folder 211)
  - Engelhard, Charles, Foundation, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 212)
  - Ensinger, Stuart, 1965-1979 (Box 16, Folder 213)
  - Environmental Education Project / Allen F. Rodney, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 214)
  - Erickson, Frances E. - Estate of, 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 215)
  - Erickson, Melinda, 1974-1976 (Box 16, Folder 216)
  - Esperat, Oswaldo, 1970-1973 (Box 16, Folder 217)
  - Espina, A. Beaunoni, 1962-1979 (Box 16, Folder 218)
  - Espy, R. H. Edwin, 1974-1979 (Box 16, Folder 219)
  - Eubank, Bransford, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 219)
  - Euclid Foundation, 1967-1978 (Box 16, Folder 220)
  - Evans, William H., 1962-1976 (Box 17, Folder 221)
  - Everton, John Scott, 1964-1981 (Box 17, Folder 222)
  - Exter, John and Marion, 1973-1979 (Box 17, Folder 223)
  - Fa - Fu (Box 17, Folder 224-229)
  - Fairbank, John K., 1973-1978 (Box 17, Folder 230)
  - Fairfield, John F., 1965-1979 (Box 18, Folder 231)
  - Fairfield, Wynn C., 1961 (Box 18, Folder 231)
  - Faith United Protestant Church, 1961-1970 (Box 18, Folder 232)
  - Faix, Thomas L., 1978 (Box 18, Folder 233)
  - Fallon, Jayne, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 234)
  - Fan, Winston, 1958-1967 (Box 18, Folder 235)
  - Farley, Malcolm and Neva, 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 236)
  - Farnham, Elizabeth R., 1963-1975 (Box 18, Folder 237)
  - Farnham, Ruth R., 1963-1975 (Box 18, Folder 237)
  - Faucett, Lawrence, 1960-1968 (Box 18, Folder 238)
  - Federation of Institutions for Marine and Freshwater Sciences, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 239)
  - Fee, Walter R., 1966-1979 (Box 18, Folder 240)
  - Fellers, Rufus G., 1971 (Box 18, Folder 241)
  - Fellows Conferences, 1971-1976 (Box 18, Folder 242-247)
  - Fellowship policies, 1963-1974 (Box 19, Folder 248)
  - Fellowship program evaluations, 1960-1975 (Box 19, Folder 249)
  - Fellowship reimbursement policy, 1966-1976 (Box 19, Folder 250)
  - Fenn, A. S., 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 251)
  - Fenn, William P., Lectures, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 252)
  - Fenn, William P. -General correspondence, 1971-1979 (Box 19, Folder 253)
  - Fenn, William P. -Corres. re. Christian Higher Education in Changing China manuscript, 1973-1976 (Box 19, Folder 254,255)
  - Fenn, William P.-Retirement tributes, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 256)
  - Ferguson, John C., 1968 (Box 19, Folder 257)
  - Ferguson, Lee H., 1961-1975 (Box 19, Folder 257)
  - Ferguson, Mary E., 1972-1979 (Box 19, Folder 257)
  - Ficken, Clarence E., 1963-1967 (Box 19, Folder 258)
  - Field, E. Beverley, 1973-1975 (Box 19, Folder 259)
  - First Congregational Church, Cheshire CT, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 260)
  - First Congregational Church, Guilford CT, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 260)
  - First National Bank, Clinton IA, 1967-1969 (Box 19, Folder 260)
  - First Presbyterian Churches - CT, MO, NC, NY, 1968-1975 (Box 19, Folder 261)
  - Fishbach, Eulalia, 1971-1975 (Box 19, Folder 262)
  - Fisher, Edwin O., 1966-1979 (Box 19, Folder 262)
  - Fisk, Larry, 1970 (Box 19, Folder 263)
  - Fisken, A. D., 1959-1967 (Box 19, Folder 263)
  - Fitch, George and Geraldine, 1962-1979 (Box 19, Folder 264)
  - Fitzhugh, Peggy, 1961-1963 (Box 19, Folder 265)
  - Flaherty, Donald, 1971-1979 (Box 20, Folder 266)
  - Fleming, John R., 1963-1979 (Box 20, Folder 267)
  - Flodin, Ivan A., 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 268)
  - Flores, Frank G., 1964-1978 (Box 20, Folder 269)
  - Flores, Pedro B., 1974 (Box 20, Folder 269)
  - Flossmoor Community Church, IL, 1961-1967 (Box 20, Folder 270)
  - Fontana Community Church, CA, 1961-1967 (Box 20, Folder 271)
  - Ford Foundation, 1968-1974 (Box 20, Folder 272)
  - Forest Fund, 1968-1979 (Box 20, Folder 272)
  - Forman Christian College, Pakistan, 1965-1978 (Box 20, Folder 273)
  - Formosan Christians for Self-Determination, 1977-1978 (Box 20, Folder 274)
  - Found, Norman, 1965-1968 (Box 20, Folder 275)
  - Foundation for Theological Education in Southeast Asia, 1965-1974 (Box 20, Folder 275)
  - Fowler, H. Seymour, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 276)
  - Fowler, Newton, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 276)
  - Foy, Ruth N., 1966-1979 (Box 20, Folder 277)
  - Frame, Margaret A., 1959-1965 (Box 20, Folder 278)
  - Franklin Book Programs Inc., 1967-1978 (Box 20, Folder 279)
  - Franklin, James H. - Estate of, 1961 (Box 20, Folder 280)
  - Franklin, Rachel G., 1958-1979 (Box 20, Folder 280)
  - Free University, Amsterdam, 1971-1978 (Box 20, Folder 281)
  - Freeman, Mansfield, 1965-1979 (Box 20, Folder 282)
  - Frei, Ernest J., 1961-1979 (Box 20, Folder 283)
  - French, Alma Louise - Estate of, 1965-1969 (Box 20, Folder 284)
  - French, Clara M., 1962-1976 (Box 21, Folder 285)
  - Freundel, Jane E., 1975 (Box 21, Folder 285)
  - Frick, Bertha M., 1964-1965 (Box 21, Folder 286)
  - Frick report on libraries in East Asia, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 287-288)
  - Fried, Paul G., 1969 (Box 21, Folder 289)
  - Friedrichs, Robert W., 1971-1976 (Box 21, Folder 289)
  - Frohne, William C., 1969 (Box 21, Folder 290)
  - Frost, Loraine H., 1970-1979 (Box 21, Folder 290)
  - Fu, Philip and Gail, 1964-1976 (Box 21, Folder 291)
  - Fu Jen Catholic University, 1974-1979 (Box 21, Folder 292)
  - Fugh, Philip, 1961-1964 (Box 21, Folder 293)
  - Fuller, Charles P. G., 1964-1978 (Box 21, Folder 294)
  - Fulton, Robert Brank, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 295)
  - Furuya, Keiichi, 1979 (Box 21, Folder 296)
  - Ga - Gi (Box 21, Folder 297-299)
  - Gl - Gz (Box 22, Folder 300-304)
  - Gale, Grant O., 1969-1974 (Box 22, Folder 305)
  - Galusha, Elinor, 1971-1979 (Box 22, Folder 306)
  - Gamble, Philip L., 1964-1969 (Box 22, Folder 307)
  - Gamble, Sidney and Elizabeth, 1953-1979 (Box 22, Folder 308)
  - Gambrell, Charles G. and Sarah, 1968-1978 (Box 22, Folder 309)
  - Ganfield, A. Boardman, 1967-1979 (Box 22, Folder 310)
  - Gantz, Gerald M., 1962-1966 (Box 22, Folder 311)
  - Garber, Paul L., 1966-1969 (Box 22, Folder 311)
  - Garnett, W. Leslie, 1973-1979 (Box 22, Folder 312)
  - Garside, B. A., 1969-1979 (Box 22, Folder 313)
  - Gates, Robert H., 1970-1978 (Box 23, Folder 314)